(087)9171424 (01) 8404295

Personal Statement

Paul McQuade

paulmcquad@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/paulmcquad/

Personal Statement

An ambitious individual who enjoys taking on responsibility and has a successful background in retail.

- A good problem solver who enjoys helping people as much as possible.
- Enjoys being part of a successful and productive team.
- Excellent written, interpersonal and analytical skills.
- Willingness to learn.

Educational Training

QQI L5: Retail Practice / 2015 - 2017 - Eve Plantmarket, Lusk Modules: Retail Selling, Retail Display, Customer Service, Marketing Practice, Work Experience, Work Processing, Communications and Health and Safety

QQI L5: (Merit) Computer Architecture / 2012 - 2013 - Roslyn Park College, Sandymount

Modules: RAM, HDD, CPU/GPU, sound cards and motherboard

QQI L5: (Distinction) Computer Programming / 2012 - 2013 - Roslyn Park College, Sandymount

Modules: VB.NET, Java, Web/ Game Development

QQI L6: (Higher Certificate) in Electronic Engineering / 2006 - 2008 - ITT Dublin, Tallaght

Modules: Year 1: Maths, Analogue/Digital Electronics, Physics, Electrical science, Computer Programming Year 2: Maths, Analogue/ Digital Electronics, Network Systems, Telecommunications

Leaving Certificate / 2004 - 2006 - Fingal Community College, Swords

Skills

QQI L5: Occupational First Aid / Fire Safety / Manual Handling / 2018 Full Clean EU Driving Licence / 2015

Career Summary

Groundskeeper / 2019 - Present - Swords Tennis Club - Swords Recreation Development (SRD)

Tourist Officer / 2018 - 2019 - Swords Castle - Swords Recreation Development (SRD)

Retail Assistant / 2 weeks - October 2016 - Centra Rivervalley Shopping Centre, Swords

Bar Staff / 2008 - 2010 - Peacock's Steakhouse - Rivervalley Shopping Centre, Swords

Bar Staff / 2006 - 2007 - The Old Boro - Main Street, Swords

Career Responsibilities

- Required a good attention to detail
- Cleaned the courts and manage money for events
- Give tours of Swords Castle and give out maps
- Cleaned the bar, changing kegs, filled fridges and tracked stock levels
- Coordinated regular intervals on cleaning tables and glasses during the night
- Managed a money float and collected customers orders
- Welcomed customers and presented great customer service
- Team player worked closely with fellow staff

IT Skills & Interests

Expert knowledge of Operating Systems like / Linux, Unix, Windows

- Manjaro Linux, Ubuntu, Debian, Linux Mint, Arch Linux, Kali Linux, Fedora,
- CentOS, Red Hat, FreeBSD, OpenBSD, NetBSD, Windows 98 SE Windows 10

Strong knowledge of Office Software like / MS Office, LibreOffice, Google Docs

Strong knowledge of Web Browser Software like / Firefox, Opera, Chrome

Knowledge of Programming like / Web Development, Scripting, Databases, Libraries

- Walking, Socializing with friends and Coder Forge members, Watching movies,
- Shopping in Pavillions Shopping Centre
- Going to the restaurants, cl and the gym

Character References

Available on request